# **David Fuentez**

# **Computer Engineer**

LinkedIn Profile: linkedin.com/in/name

daniel367daniel367@gmail.com +504-9825-2225

 $\Theta$ 

Click here for my portfolio

## **PERSONAL SUMMARY**

I am a Software Developer, ERP Systems, mobile applications and Web Applications. Skilled in data analysis, software engineering. Solid education professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Engineering from the Technological University of Honduras. English teacher with demonstrable experience in the non-profit management sector.



## **Academic Education**

#### Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science | Universidad Tecnológica de Honduras

Completion date: May 2024



# **Work Experience**

#### FullStack Developer | Blessing to the Nations Ministry (june 2023 - present)

- Development of management systems for the control of sales, inventories, suppliers, reports and invoicing of a coffee company.
- Development of web applications for project management in NGOs.
- Development of web applications for the administrative and information management of schools.
- Construction of user interfaces, database development, implementation of API's.
- Environments and Technologies: Java, C#, C++, JavaScript, Next.js, CSS, HTML, Firebase, GIT, GitHub, node.js, Vercel, JSON.

#### Financial Assistant Analyst | Blessing to the Nations Ministry Part-Time (january 2022 - present)

- Financial reporting and Data deployment in Power Bl.
- Analysis of financial information for project decisions.

#### Mobile Application Developer | Blessing to the Nations Ministry Part-Time (january 2024 - december 2024)

- Development of mobile applications for NGOs.
- User interface construction, database development, API implementation.
- Environments and Technologies: Dart, Flutter, Firebase, GIT, GitHub.

#### Teacher/Tutor | Proyecto Nueva Vida (january 2020 - december 2024)

- Computer Science and Mathematics classes from 2nd to 9th grade.
- Achievements: Increased individual student performance.
- Planning of the class schedule.

# Certifications

#### Certification in Power BI: Data Analysis and Business Intelligence

UDEMY June 2024

#### Certification in NDG Linux Essentials y NDG Linux Unhatched | Cisco Networking Academy

• 2023

# Certification in 5G tecnologies, AI, Cloud Computing y HMS | Huawei, Seeds for The Future Class octubre 2022

Program Seeds for the Future from Huawei.

## Certification in Master en JavaScript: Aprender JS, jQuery, Angular, NodeJS

• UDEMY Junio 2023

#### **Certification in Typescript: The Complete developers Guide**

• UDEMY Junio 2023

#### Skills

- Developer in Flutter, Net Maui, LAMP, HTML, CSS JavaScript, Java, C# environments.
- Power Bl, Java, HTML, CSS, Python, Excel, Firebase, MySQL, Oracle Database, NextJs, Microsoft Word.
- Experience in Adobe Photoshop and video editing.

# Languages

- English Language
- Spanish Language

# **Volunteers**

- Volunteer at Samaritans Purse, Operation Christmas Child children's charity program.
- Project leader at Ministry Blessing to the Nations, in the Agua Pura project, to provide 500 families living in remote communities with access to clean water in Honduras.
- I have participated as an English to Spanish interpreter in medical and social brigades in remote communities in Honduras.